(Amy:)Well, if you're nervous
about the sleeping arrangements,
(Amy:)maybe we should talk about it.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Talk.
(Amy:)Well, I imagine
one of your concerns
(Amy:)might be coital
expectations.
(Sheldon:)Wow, no foreplay or anything,
just right to it.
(Amy:)Look, I know
this experiment
(Amy:)is a big step outside
of your comfort zone.
(Amy:)So why don't we take being
physical off the table
(Amy:)and maybe later on,
(Amy:)once we're more settled in,
we can revisit it.
(Sheldon:)You're really okay with that?
(Amy:)I've never lived
with someone, either.
(Amy:)This is a lot for me, too.
(Sheldon:)This is such a relief.
(Sheldon:)Honestly, if it didn't
get you all worked up,
(Sheldon:)I'd kiss you right now.
(Amy:)Good call.
(Amy:)Seeing your
Teen Titans underwear
(Amy:)really got my
motor running.
(Sheldon:)I know. They probably shouldn't
sell those to children.